Hello friends, today we will talk about
repairing the front part * Millers
Insurance Claim. Often we understand
that the front rock of your choice will be replaced
or it will be repaired, so today we will talk on this topic
that when should you agree to repair the front part
and when should you
insist for replacement, then if there is an
accident of the two wheeler then it will either
fall on the left side or it will fall on the right side
and falling on one side will cause its alignment to be disturbed, let
us see if your two wheeler has
less damage then by doing a simple alignment
its damage will be fixed and
you will be able to use the same bike again, if there is
more damage in it then in such a condition
your Focus MB will be replaced, how can we check whether the
damage in your Focus MB is less or more,
see, there are probably two
locks on the right side and one on the left side, if
both these boxes are
your handles that control the mandrel, press them and do
stunts on the left side,
if our two wheeler falls down with more force then it is
expected that these will be the ones and
if these are the ones then your  It
should be replaced, so now let's talk about that young man went
and after we went and
completed the documentation, Vikram
tweeted and Bigg Boss
came back from us and subscribe and
change it, so in such a condition we check
that by Whatsapping us and we are
replacing it, if there is ghee in your family and
after doing it,
that condition is fine, if there
is a damaged dada in your family, its locks should be replaced directly, but on the
advice of the insurance company, Moksha is given on the insistence of the insurance company,
after getting it repaired for the same family, you
put it in the physical, then this condition is wrong,
in such a condition even the manufacturer never
reminds that if the for assembly
election is Amit and after getting those people repaired,
now use them in this, the
manufacturer does not recruit force in this condition,
they themselves make the repayment from it, that
in such a condition the for assembly should be
replaced,
insurance claim a second  The condition is that
when a WhatsApper
sells an assembly for repair, then he
charges the insurance company for ₹100, from ₹600
to ₹100 plus GST extra and
in actual its cost will be ₹200 to
₹300.
They get a good commission in any repair, so the worker
himself inquires that he will mostly
repair the assembly, but there are many
people in it who are in the world of box repair and chilli
alignment, so in such a condition they will
only replace it, if there is alignment
cost in it, it is possible for you to become popular,
so they always inquire that they will only
repair it, instead of replacement,
see in insurance claims or it is your
duty to go yourself and send a WhatsApp message
whether the parts are being replaced in the world
and which
parts in your option are being used after repair
and if you have any problem then
talk to the insurance company and
talk through WhatsApp  Do this so that you can get a
justified answer as to
what is the reaction of the parts that are being replaced
and what is the reaction of the parts that are being replaced.
So we hope that today's video
will clear the safe points as to when to get the fire assembly
repaired and when to insist on replacement of the fire assembly.